https://www.perkinsrestaurants.com/california-privacy-request/

California Privacy Request
California residents have the right to submit privacy requests regarding their personal data. Please fill out the form if you are a California resident and you wish to make a request in accordance with your privacy rights. Please include all the information below so we can verify and process your request.
Name*
First
Last
Email*
Phone*State of Residence*AlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyomingArmed Forces AmericasArmed Forces EuropeArmed Forces PacificRequest Type*Right to Request Categories and Specific Pieces of Personal InformationRight to Request Deletion of Personal InformationRight to Request Collected Personal InformationRight to Request Sold or Disclosed Personal InformationRight to Opt OutRight Against DiscriminationPlease Describe Your Request**
This iframe contains the logic required to handle Ajax powered Gravity Forms.
WE COLLECT YOUR FIRST NAME, LAST NAME, EMAIL ADDRESS, PHONE NUMBER AND IP ADDRESS INFORMATION SOLELY IN ORDER TO PROCESS AND VERIFY YOUR PRIVACY REQUEST ACCORDING TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY.
Company
Careers
Franchise
Contact Us
Privacy
CCPA
Legal Info
Perkins Restaurant & Bakery is an ASCENT Hospitality Management brand.
